Not it's not just react.
Non  non solo reagire.
There are also alternatives re-act of course is what we'll cover in this course.
Ci sono anche alternative al re-act, naturalmente,  ci che copriremo in questo corso.
But there also is Engler and there would be viewed chaos and there are avarice like backbone or amber
Ma c' anche Engler e si vedrebbe il caos e ci sono avarizia come spina dorsale o
but angular and view are the most popular alternatives.
ambra ma angolare e vista sono le alternative pi popolari.
And I can only recommend diving into DS to to really pick your favorite.
E posso solo consigliare di immergerti in DS per scegliere davvero il tuo preferito.
I also got courses on them if you are interested.
Ho anche corsi su di loro se sei interessato.
All three of them are great at creating highly scalable web applications that look and feel good to
Tutti e tre sono perfetti nella creazione di applicazioni web altamente scalabili che
the user.
siano gradevoli all'utilizzatore.
Not so much an alternative as Jake where he you might think it is one but Shakeri is really only about
Non tanto un'alternativa come Jake dove si potrebbe pensare che sia uno, ma Shakeri  in realt solo di attraversare
traversing the dorm and targeting elements in a dorm.
il dormitorio e gli elementi di targeting in un dormitorio.
Now as you saw in our example re-act is about just declaring what you see and focusing on the logic
Ora come hai visto nel nostro esempio re-act  solo dichiarare ci che vedi e concentrarti
instead on focusing on the how and therefore react angular and view allow you to create more powerful
sulla logica invece concentrarti sul come e quindi reagire angolare e vista ti permettono di creare applicazioni
applications because you can focus on the logic and your business model and not so much on the technical
pi potenti perch puoi concentrarti sulla logica e il tuo modello di business e non tanto
side of actually reaching dead element.
sul lato tecnico dell'effettivo raggiungimento dell'elemento morto.
You wanted to change.
Volevi cambiare.